





PMEC Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ASP.NET, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Web Services, JSON, C#.NET, Ajax, REACT JS

Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer

Current Company: Capgemini
Current Location: Pune
Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore,Pune,Bhopal

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

ivaintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Consultant, Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ASP.NET, JavaScript, Query, HTML5, CSS3, Web

Services, JSON, C#.NET, Ajax, REACT JS, Team Leader

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

### **Summary**

5.5 years of work experience in development, enhancement and support applications. Comprehensive knowledge of REACT JS, C#.NET, ASP.NET, VB.NET, MS SQL Server 2008, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, Ajax, Bootstrap2/3. Familiar with version control tools like TFS.

## **Work Experience**

- Capgemini as Senior Software Engineer Mar 2020 to Till Date
- Capgemini as Consultant -Dot Net

Mar 2020 to Jul 2020

Project Name:

Overview

Technologies

AutomationTools SogetiTesting

SogetiTesting is an integral project of Capgemini.It is an internal project with a focus to provide rich user experience and to support various devices like mobiles and tablets.

The objectives of the project are

- 1. Creating and executing the test cases
   2. Installation of Eclipse, Selenium Webdriver,
   3. Execution of test scenarios in selenium
   HTML, CSS, Javascript, Advanced Javascript, MVC, WebApi, REACT JS
   Selenium Webdriver Postman
- Larsen and Toubro Infotech as Sr. Software Engineer Jan 2019 to Jan 2020
  - 1. Project Name: Marsh and McMellan Corporation(MMC)

#### Overview

MMC is ClientBasedProject which is basically Windows Based Application which basically uses two forms MTrack and MTrack

Manager to provide user rich experience.

The chiectives of the project are

# 1

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

- 1.Migrate from Vbnet to C# using Component FlexGrid
- 2. Creating new forms Mtrack and MTrack Manager
- 3.Resolving compile time errors after conversion 4. Interacting withn QA team at testing level
- 5.Deployed the code.

Technologies VB.Net

Role: Design and development as per the client requirement. Client(s):

MMC

Cognizant as Associate Jan 2015 to Jan 2019

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Oriental College Of Technology, Bhopal in 2014

^ Back to Top

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
WINDOWS			
Microsoft Sql Server 2008R2			
ASP.NET			
JavaScript			
JQUERY			
HTML5, CSS3			
IIS 7.0 Server			
WEB SERVICES			
JSON			
C#.NET			
AJAX			
React js			
Visual Studio 2010/2012/ 2013/2015			
TFS			

^ Back to Top

#### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In İndia All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.